Office of the Provost. Administrative files of Ernest Carroll Moore. 1917-1936. UARC.0261
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Conferences - Assoc. of Colleges and University of the Pacific Southerwest., 1932-1933. (Box 47)
- Conferences - University Religious Conference., 1932-1933. (Box 47)
- Conferences - Western Association of Colleges and Secondary Schools., 1932-1933. (Box 47)
- Conferences - Western Association of Colleges and Secondary Schools., 1932-1933. (Box 47)
- Deans - College of Letters and Science., 1932-1933. (Box 47)
- Deans - Men., 1932-1933. (Box 47)
- Deans - Teachers College., 1932-1933. (Box 47)
- Deans - Women., 1932-1933. (Box 47)
- Departments - Agriculture., 1932-1933. (Box 47)
- Departments - Art., 1932-1933. (Box 47)
- Departments - Astronomy., 1932-1933. (Box 47)
- Departments - Chemistry., 1932-1933. (Box 47)
- Departments - Economics., 1932-1933. (Box 47)
- Departments - English., 1932-1933. (Box 47)
- Departments - Extension., 1932-1933. (Box 47)
- Departments - Geography., 1932-1933. (Box 47)
- Departments - Geology., 1932-1933. (Box 47)
- Departments - History., 1932-1933. (Box 47)
- Departments - Languages, Classical., 1932-1933. (Box 47)
- Departments - Languages, French., 1932-1933. (Box 47)
- Departments - Languages, German., 1932-1933. (Box 47)
- Departments - Languages, Spanish., 1932-1933. (Box 47)
- Departments - Health Service., 1932-1933. (Box 47, Folder 1)
- Departments - Library., 1932-1933. (Box 48)
- Departments - Mathematics., 1932-1933. (Box 48)
- Departments - Mechanic Arts., 1932-1933. (Box 48)
- Departments - Military Science and Tactics., 1932-1933. (Box 48)
- Departments - Music., 1932-1933. (Box 48)
- Departments - Philosophy., 1932-1933. (Box 48)
- Departments - Physical Education for Men., 1932-1933. (Box 48)
- Departments - Physical Education for Women., 1932-1933. (Box 48)
- Departments - Physics., 1932-1933. (Box 48)
- Departments - Political Science., 1932-1933. (Box 48)
- Departments - Psychology., 1932-1933. (Box 48)
- Departments - Scripps Institution of Oceanography., 1932-1933. (Box 48)
- Departments - Training Department., 1932-1933. (Box 48)
- Departments - Vocational Education Division., 1932-1933. (Box 48)
- Donations., 1932-1933. (Box 48)
- Education - City and County Offices., 1932-1933. (Box 48)
- Education -State Offices., 1932-1933. (Box 48)
- Faculty - Applications for Positions at UCLA., 1932-1933. (Box 48)
- Faculty - General Correspondence., 1932-1933. (Box 48)
- Faculty - Research and Travel Grants., 1932-1933. (Box 48)
- Faculty - Sabbatical Leaves., 1932-1933. (Box 48)
- Lectures., 1932-1933. (Box 49)
- Programs and Special Events., 1932-1933. (Box 49)
- Regents., 1932-1933. (Box 49)
- Students - ASUCLA., 1932-1933. (Box 49)
- Students - Fraternities and Sororities., 1932-1933. (Box 49)
- Students - General Correspondence., 1932-1933. (Box 49)
- Students - Student Conference Against War., 1932-1933. (Box 49)
- Students - YMCA and YWCA., 1932-1933. (Box 49)
- Survey of Higher Education in California., 1932-1933. (Box 49)
- Academic Senate., 1933-1934. (Box 50)
- Academic Senate - Graduate Council., 1933-1934. (Box 50)
- Administration, Berkeley - President's Office., 1933 Jul-Nov. (Box 50)
- General Correspondence., 1932 Jul-Dec. (Box 50)
- General Correspondence., 1933 Jun-Jan. (Box 50)
- Administration, Berkeley - General Correspondence., 1933-1934. (Box 51)
- Administration, Berkeley - President's Office., 1934 Dec-Jan. (Box 51)
- Administration, UCLA - Administrative., 1933-1934. (Box 51)
- Administration, UCLA - Admissions., 1933-1934. (Box 51)
- Administration, UCLA - Committees., 1933-1934. (Box 51)
- Administration, UCLA - Comptroller's Office., 1933-1934. (Box 51)
- Administration, UCLA - Comptroller's OFfice, Budget Statements., 1933-1934. (Box 51)
- Administration, UCLA - Graduate Workd., 1933-1934. (Box 51)
- Administration, UCLA - Registrar., 1933-1934. (Box 52)
- Administration, UCLA - Secretary, Appointment., 1933-1934. (Box 52)
- Administration, UCLA - University Associates., 1933-1934. (Box 52)
- Alumni., 1933-1934. (Box 52)
- Conferences - University Regilious Conference., 1933-1934. (Box 52)
- Conferences - Western Association of Colleges and Secondary Schools., 1933-1934. (Box 52)
- Deans - College of Letter and Science., 1933-1934. (Box 52)
- Deans - Men., 1933-1934. (Box 52)
- Deans - Summer Session., 1933-1934. (Box 52)
- Deans - Teachers College., 1933-1934. (Box 52)
- Deans - Women., 1933-1934. (Box 52)
- Del Amo Foundation., 1933-1934. (Box 52)
- Department - Home Economics., 1933-1934. (Box 52)
- Departments - Agriculture., 1933-1934. (Box 52)
- Departments - Annual Report of Ernest C. Moore., 1933-1934. (Box 52)
- Departments - Art., 1933-1934. (Box 52)
- Departments - Astronomy., 1933-1934. (Box 52)
- Departments - Biological Sciences., 1933-1934. (Box 52)
- Departments - Chemistry., 1933-1934. (Box 52)
- Departments - Economics., 1933-1934. (Box 52)
- Departments - Education., 1933-1934. (Box 52)
- Departments - English., 1933-1934. (Box 52)
- Departments - Geography., 1933-1934. (Box 52)
- Departments - Geology., 1933-1934. (Box 52)
- Departments - Health Service., 1933-1934. (Box 52)
- Departments - History., 1933-1934. (Box 52)
- Departments - Languages, Classical., 1933-1934. (Box 52)
- Departments - Languages, French., 1933-1934. (Box 52)
- Departments - Languages, German., 1933-1934. (Box 52)
- Departments - Languages, Spanish., 1933-1934. (Box 52)
- Departments - Library., 1933-1934. (Box 52)
- Departments - Mathematics., 1933-1934. (Box 52)
- Departments - Mechanic Arts., 1933-1934. (Box 52)
- Departments - Military Science and Tactics., 1933-1934. (Box 52)
- Departments - Military Training at UCLA, Public Response., 1933-1934. (Box 53)
- Departments - Music., 1933-1934. (Box 53)
- Departments - Philosophy., 1933-1934. (Box 53)
- Departments - Physical Education for Men., 1933-1934. (Box 53)
- Departments - Physical Education for Women., 1933-1934. (Box 53)
- Departments - Physics., 1933-1934. (Box 53)
- Departments - Political Science., 1933-1934. (Box 53)
- Departments - Psychology., 1933-1934. (Box 53)
- Departments - Scripps Institution of Oceangraphy., 1933-1934. (Box 53)
- Departments - Training Department., 1933-1934. (Box 53)
- Departments - Vocational Education Division., 1933-1934. (Box 53)
- Donations., 1933-1934. (Box 53)
- Education - City and County Offices., 1933-1934. (Box 53)
- Education - State Offices., 1933-1934. (Box 53)
- Faculty - Applications for Positions at UCLA., 1933-1934. (Box 53)
- Faculty - Research and Travel Requests., 1933-1934. (Box 53)
- Faculty - General Correspondence., 1933-1934. (Box 54)
- Faculty - Sabbatical Leaves., 1933-1934. (Box 54)
- Lectures, Program and Special Events - Charter Day., 1933-1934. (Box 54)
- Lectures, Programs and Special Events., 1933-1934. (Box 54)
- Regents., 1933-1934. (Box 54)
- Students - ASUCLA., 1933-1934. (Box 54)
- Students - Fraternities and Sororities., 1933-1934. (Box 54)
- Students - General Correspondence., 1933-1934. (Box 54)
- Academic Senate., 1934-1935. (Box 55)
- Administration, Berkeley - President's Office., 1934 Jul-Dec. (Box 55)
- Administration, Berkeley - President's Office., 1935 Jan-Jun. (Box 55)
- General Correspondence., 1933 Jul-1934 Feb. (Box 55)
- General Correspondence., 1934 Mar-Jun. (Box 55)
- Administration, UCLA - Administrative Staff Meetings., 1934-1935. (Box 56)
- Administration, UCLA - Committees., 1934-1935. (Box 56)
- Administration, UCLA - Comptroller's Office., 1934-1935. (Box 56)
- Administration, UCLA - Comptroller's Office, Budget Statements., 1934-1935. (Box 56)
- Administration, UCLA - Registrar., 1934-1935. (Box 56)
- Administration, UCLA - Secretary, Appointment., 1934-1935. (Box 56)
- Administration, UCLA - University Associates., 1934-1935. (Box 56)
- Adminstration, UCLA - Admissions., 1934-1935. (Box 56)
- Alumni., 1934-1935. (Box 56)
- Conferences - University Religious Conference., 1934-1935. (Box 56)
- Dean - College of Letter and Science., 1934-1935. (Box 56)
- Deans - Graduate Study., 1934-1935. (Box 56)
- Deans - Men., 1934-1935. (Box 56)
- Deans - Summer Session., 1934-1935. (Box 56)
- Deans - Teacher College., 1934-1935. (Box 56)
- Deans - Women., 1934-1935. (Box 56)
- Del Amo Foundation., 1934-1935. (Box 56)
- Departments - Agriculture., 1934-1935. (Box 56)
- Departments - Art., 1934-1935. (Box 56)
- Departments - Astronomy., 1934-1935. (Box 56)
- Departments - Chemistry., 1934-1935. (Box 56)
- Departments - Economics., 1934-1935. (Box 56)
- Departments - Education., 1934-1935. (Box 56)
- Departments - English., 1934-1935. (Box 56)
- Departments - Geography., 1934-1935. (Box 56)
- Departments - Geology., 1934-1935. (Box 56)
- Departments - Health Service., 1934-1935. (Box 56)
- Departments - History., 1934-1935. (Box 56)
- Departments - Home Economics., 1934-1935. (Box 56)
- Departments - Languages, Classical., 1934-1935. (Box 56)
- Departments - Languages, French., 1934-1935. (Box 56)
- Departments - Languages, German., 1934-1935. (Box 57)
- Departments - Languages, Spanish., 1934-1935. (Box 57)
- Departments - Library., 1934-1935. (Box 57)
- Departments - Library, Clark., 1934-1935. (Box 57)
- Departments - Lige Sciences., 1934-1935. (Box 57)
- Departments - Mathematics., 1934-1935. (Box 57)
- Departments - Mechanic Arts., 1934-1935. (Box 57)
- Departments - Military Science and Tactics., 1934-1935. (Box 57)
- Departments - Military Training at UCLA., 1934-1935. (Box 57)
- Departments - Music., 1934-1935. (Box 57)
- Departments - Philosophy., 1934-1935. (Box 57)
- Departments - Physical Education for Men., 1934-1935. (Box 57)
- Departments - Physical Education for Women., 1934-1935. (Box 57)
- Departments - Physics., 1934-1935. (Box 57)
- Departments - Political Science., 1934-1935. (Box 57)
- Departments - Psychology., 1934-1935. (Box 57)
- Departments - Scripps Institution of Oceanography., 1934-1935. (Box 57)
- Departments - Training Department., 1934-1935. (Box 57)
- Donations., 1934-1935. (Box 57)
- Education - City and County Offices., 1934-1935. (Box 57)
- Education - State Offices., 1934-1935. (Box 57)
- Faculty - Applications for Positions at UCLA., 1934-1935. (Box 58)
- Faculty - General Correspondence., 1934-1935. (Box 58)
- Faculty - Sabbatical Leaves, Research and Travel Grants., 1934-1935. (Box 58)
- Lectures, Programs and Special Events., 1934-1935. (Box 58)
- Lectures, Programs and Special Events - Charter Day., 1934-1935. (Box 58)
- Regents., 1934-1935. (Box 58)
- Students - Alcohol on Campus., 1934-1935. (Box 58)
- Students - ASUCLA., 1934-1935. (Box 58)
- Students - General Correspondence., 1934-1935. (Box 58)
- Students - Suspension of Student Activists., 1934 Aug-Nov. (Box 58)
- Student - Suspension of Student Activists., n.d. (Box 59)
- Students - Suspension of Students., 1934 Nov. (Box 59)
- Students - Suspension of Student Activists., 1934 Nov-Dec. (Box 59)
- Students - Suspension of Student Activists., 1935 Jan-Jun. (Box 59)
- Academic Senate., 1935-1936. (Box 60)
- Academic Senate - Graduate Council., 1935-1936. (Box 60)
- Administratio, Berkeley - President's Office., 1935 Jul-Oct. (Box 60)
- Administration, Berkeley - President's Office., 1935 Nov-1936 Jun. (Box 60)
- General Correspondence., 1934 Jul-Dec. (Box 60)
- General Correspondence., 1935 Jan-Jun. (Box 60)
- Administration, UCLA - Admissions., 1935-1936. (Box 61)
- Administration, UCLA - Committees., 1935-1936. (Box 61)
- Administration, UCLA - Comptroller's Office., 1935-1936. (Box 61)
- Administration, UCLA - Comptroller's Office, Budget Statements., 1935-1936. (Box 61)
- Administration, UCLA - Registrar., 1935-1936. (Box 61)
- Administration, UCLA - Secretary, Appointment., 1935-1936. (Box 61)
- Alumni., 1935-1936. (Box 61)
- Board of Research, UC., 1935-1936. (Box 61)
- Conferences - University Religious Conference., 1935-1936. (Box 61)
- Deans - College of Letters and Science., 1935-1936. (Box 61)
- Deans - Graduate Study., 1935-1936. (Box 61)
- Deans - Men., 1935-1936. (Box 61)
- Deans - Summer Session., 1935-1936. (Box 61)
- Deans - Teachers College., 1935-1936. (Box 61)
- Deans - Women., 1935-1936. (Box 61)
- Department - Library., 1935-1936. (Box 61)
- Departments - Agriculture., 1935-1936. (Box 61)
- Departments - Anthropology., 1935-1936. (Box 61)
- Departments - Art., 1935-1936. (Box 61)
- Departments - Astronomy., 1935-1936. (Box 61)
- Departments - Business Administration., 1935-1936. (Box 61)
- Departments - Chemistry., 1935-1936. (Box 61)
- Departments - Economics., 1935-1936. (Box 61)
- Departments - Education., 1935-1936. (Box 61)
- Departments - English., 1935-1936. (Box 61)
- Departments - Extension., 1935-1936. (Box 61)
- Departments - Geography., 1935-1936. (Box 61)
- Departments - Geology., 1935-1936. (Box 61)
- Departments - Health Service., 1935-1936. (Box 61)
- Departments - Health Service., 1935-1936. (Box 61)
- Departments - History., 1935-1936. (Box 61)
- Departments - Home Economics., 1935-1936. (Box 61)
- Departments - Language, Classical., 1935-1936. (Box 61)
- Departments - Language, French., 1935-1936. (Box 61)
- Departments - Language, Spanish., 1935-1936. (Box 61)
- Departments - Languages, German., 1935-1936. (Box 61)
- Departments - Languages, Italian., 1935-1936. (Box 61)
- Departments - Languages, Italian., 1935-1936. (Box 61)
- Departments - Library, Clark., 1935-1936. (Box 61)
- Departments - Life Science., 1935-1936. (Box 61)
- Departments - Mathematics., 1935-1936. (Box 61)
- Department - Physical Education for Women., 1935-1936. (Box 62)
- Departments - Military Science and Tactics., 1935-1936. (Box 62)
- Departments - Music., 1935-1936. (Box 62)
- Departments - Philosophy., 1935-1936. (Box 62)
- Departments - Physical Education for Men., 1935-1936. (Box 62)
- Departments - Physics., 1935-1936. (Box 62)
- Departments - Political Science., 1935-1936. (Box 62)
- Departments - Psychology., 1935-1936. (Box 62)
- Departments - Training Department., 1935-1936. (Box 62)
- Departments - Vocational Education., 1935-1936. (Box 62)
- Donations., 1935-1936. (Box 62)
- Education - City and County Offices., 1935-1936. (Box 62)
- Education - State Offices., 1935-1936. (Box 62)
- Faculty - Applications for Positions at UCLA., 1935 Jul-Dec. (Box 62)
- Faculty - Applications for Positions at UCLA., 1936 Jan-Jun. (Box 62)
- Faculty - General Correspondence., 1935-1936. (Box 63)
- Faculty - Sabbatical Leaves, Research and Travel Grants., 1935-1936. (Box 63)
- Lectures, Programs and Special Events., 1935-1936. (Box 63)
- Regents., 1935-1936. (Box 63)
- Students - Activism and Disciplinary., 1935-1936. (Box 63)
- Students - ASUCLA., 1935-1936. (Box 63)
- Students - General Correspondence., 1935-1936. (Box 63)
- Administration, Berkeley - President's Office., n.d. (Box 64)
- Administration, UCLA - Committees., n.d. (Box 64)
- Administration, UCLA - Comptroller's Office., n.d. (Box 64)
- Administration, UCLA - Registrar., n.d. (Box 64)
- Buildings and Landscaping. (Box 64)
- Departments - Chemistry., n.d. (Box 64)
- Departments - Economics., n.d. (Box 64)
- Departments - History., n.d. (Box 64)
- Departments - Languages, French., n.d. (Box 64)
- Departments - Philosophy., n.d. (Box 64)
- Departments - Physics., n.d. (Box 64)
- Departments - Political Science., n.d. (Box 64)
- Departments - Psychology., n.d. (Box 64)
- Departments - Pyschology., n.d. (Box 64)
- Faculty - General Correspondence. (Box 64)
- General Correspondence., 1935-1936. (Box 64)
- Infirmary, UC - Health Examination., n.d. (Box 64)
- Lectures, Programs and Speacial Events. (Box 64)
- Students - General Correspondence. (Box 64)
- N-S. Delegate letters., 1930. (Box 65)
- Dedication - miscellaneous correspondence., 1930. (Box 65)
- A-F. Delegate letters., 1930. (Box 65)
- F-M. Delegate letters., 1930. (Box 65)
- T-Z. Delegate letters., 1930. (Box 65)
- Dedication - book of., 1930-1931. (Box 65)
  Scope and Contents
  Letters of receipt, correspondence, opening remarks.
- Printed matter., 1930. (Box 65)
  Preliminary copy of program, program, information, etc.
- Dedication - program (speakers)., 1929-1930. (Box 65)
  program, notes and correspondence.
- Dedication files., 1930. (Box 66)
  List of delegates, preliminary, supplementary, and final. Errors in printed list. List of Universities and other institutions and their delegates. Listo fo committee on the dedication, and communication between members of the committee. Opening remarks by E.R. Hedrick, Thursday March 27, 130, 2 P.M. Dedication Ceremonies, UCLA etc.
- University of California., 1930. (Box 66)
  Correspondence with the President's office and with Director Moore.
- Correspondence from universities, colleges and other institutions, appointing delegates. A-M., 1930. (Box 66)
- C. Universities, colleges, etc. appointing delegates., 1930. (Box 66)
  Correspondence.
- D-E-F-G. Universities, colleges, etc. appointing delegates., 1930. (Box 66)
- H. Universities, colleges, etc. appointing delegates., 1930. (Box 66)
- I-J-K. Universities, colleges, etc. appointing delegates., 1930. (Box 66)
- L. Universities, colleges, etc. appointing delegates., 1930. (Box 66)
- M. Universities, colleges, etc. appointing delegates., 1930. (Box 66)
- N. Universities, colleges, etc. appointing delegates., 1930. (Box 66)
- O. Universities, colleges, etc. appointing delegates., 1930. (Box 66)
- P. Universities, colleges, etc. appointing delegates., 1930. (Box 66)
- R. Universities, colleges, etc. appointing delegates., 1930. (Box 66)
- S. Universities, colleges, etc. appointing delegates., 1930. (Box 66)
- T-U. Universities, colleges, etc. appointing delegates., 1930. (Box 66)
- V. Universities, colleges, etc. appointing delegates., 1930. (Box 66)
- W-X. Universities, colleges, etc. appointing delegates., 1930. (Box 66)
- Additional dedication material to be filed., 1930. (Box 66)
- Correspondence from the delegates., 1930. (Box 66)
  Letters from the delegates with their signatures.
- Addresses of dedications., 1930. (Box 66)
  Correspondence and dedication addresses.
- Dedication: invitations., 1930. (Box 66)
  From Dr. Moore's file.
- Correspondence from Universities, colleges and other institutions appointing delegates., 1930. (Box 66)
- A and B. Universities, colleges, etc. - appointing delegates., 1930. (Box 66)